.
Whirly, swirly, swirly, swirly.
Too much polyglutamic acid.
There we go.
Now it's broken up into glutamic acid.
Destruction's the essence of dragon.
Is it ready yet?
Need more.
Oh, hi.
Good morning to you.
Morning, Kobayashi.
Morning.
Hey.
Okra miso soup.
Great way to kick off summer.
Thanks for the food.
Take said there's something called a summer festival coming up?
It sounds fun.
I told Saika why I would go with her.
What do you do there?
I heard they open up lots and lots of stalls and stuff.
Where we at least land in the rain?
Sure.
Where we at least find metres,
could this plante Vegan can be achgraphed as she said.
Right.
Hour.
Hurray.
Your road is empty too.
Da-ya.
Get up here.
And you can pack some water.
Who you can pack some water.
To 말씀 which is scarce for the sake.
What age?
I want to have a...
Who you are?
That lying of no evil isilian?
Can I ask something?
What do you do when relationships start getting serious?
Huh.
Well, let me think.
I guess I just go with it.
I mean, what else can you do?
Yeah, I get that.
I definitely get that.
Hey, it's the festival they were talking about this morning.
I guess I'll go with Toru.
Ugh, do we have to get Yukadas?
She can wear one. I'm out.
They're decorating already?
Toru? What the...
Some people from the shopping district needed help.
Wow. They really have a lot of faith in you.
Well, it's a huge pain in the tail, even if it is for the festival.
You look like you were having so much fun.
Because I knew you'd pass by at any moment.
The thought of you walking under the lights I hung up makes me tingle all over.
Magical.
Hey, are you up to anything on that day?
Apparently the girls from the maid cafe will have a stall there,
so I'll probably go help them out.
Oh, cool.
Okay, then.
Wow. She seems to be adapting quite well.
She's taking initiative to truly get to know the people in our town,
working with them to build genuine connections,
and really striving to earn their trust.
I guess that's easy to do when you have the power of a dragon.
She's changed, but in a good way, I think.
I haven't.
I'm the same.
Which makes me wonder if I'm even on her level at this point.
Why does she even like me?
Whatever.
I guess it's silly to compare.
She's started bothering me less and less,
and I'm feeling more and more lonely.
Well, that's a thought that will never see the light of day.
Kobayashi, can I have this one?
Yeah.
It's so cute.
Oh, yay.
Kobayashi!
What do you think of this?
I think it would look adorable on you.
Thank you.
What about yours?
Aren't you gonna wear one?
Yeah, no.
I'm actually good.
Miss Kobayashi, which one of these do you like best?
I don't know.
Whichever one you could see yourself wearing?
Come on, don't ruin this for me.
I want you to choose, please.
Uh, okay, fine.
Eeny, meeny, miny, moe, ask God if he knows.
You put a rose on your nose and pick this one.
This one.
I'll never do anything that bastard says!
I picked this one!
Great.
Ah!
Are you having a good time, Alma?
I just love festivals so much!
I wonder what they were like in your world.
Let me think.
There was whole roasted pig, a baked chicken...
She only remembers what kind of food she ate there.
She was actually a ton of sushi!
It's Lady Toro!
Here you go, sir.
Our maid cafe specialty, Omo Rice.
Lady Toro!
Hi, Kana!
You came by!
Why are you wearing that festival uniform instead of your own maid outfit?
Eh, the maid outfit is so hard to move around in!
I figured you'd say that.
What matters most is the heart.
You have Omo Rice?
I want one, too!
Sorry, you have to go wait in line.
Hm?
She's so popular.
I can't!
If I line up here, I might miss out on eating the grilled corn and the grilled squid and the
okonomiyaki, can't eat apples and all kinds of food I like!
You're being ridiculous.
I'll bring you a souvenir plate when I come home.
Oh, Toro, you're amazing!
That would be so cool!
The tears, though.
Hey, Miss Kobayashi!
I'll be getting off in about an hour.
Copy that.
I can't get enough of the way the soy sauce smells!
I'm happy for you.
Well, hello!
Hey, Lukua and Shota.
Good evening!
Good evening.
Festivals are the best, aren't they?
Sure.
Though they are a little different here.
In our world, many festivals were held to celebrate a lot of different gods.
Oh, wow.
No one really celebrates their religion around here anymore.
Celebrating the gods made security tight, which is why the dragons couldn't get close.
Oh, yeah.
In the big country up north, they held a huge festival in the spring every year.
It was so hard to get through there that season.
The gods actually came down the place.
Blah, blah, blah.
Uh, that's all I can hear.
I mean, I like hearing about other worlds, but it also makes me feel kind of invisible.
Oh, well, whatever.
It's fine.
Got it.
Yay!
Kana, your yukata is so cute!
Thank you, Saikawa.
So is yours.
Here's an idea.
Let's come to the festival together next year.
We can do it every year until we're little old ladies together, too.
Saikawa, please live a long time.
What?
I hope to.
You and I are BFFs forever, right?
That's so cool!
Yes!
Wow!
They're all so happy.
What a great place for kids.
I always forget you're not really a kid, and then every once in a while, bang, you act way more grown up than me.
Come on!
Takei, I was actually tricked into being here.
What does that mean?
I was told I had to be an adult, and that I could never go back to being a kid.
But Kobayashi encouraged me.
She said it was okay to be a kid again.
Wow.
And yet the more mature version of you is still there.
You think so?
If giving you permission is all it takes, then count me in.
I say you can be a kid, too.
Bam!
Yeah!
Well then, guess it's my turn.
I'm gonna make you an adult.
Wait, what the heck do you mean by that?
Made you look.
Wow.
That doesn't count, suck.
I think those who knew the old you would be so surprised to see you now.
You're one to talk, since when do goddesses become familiars?
Okay, sure.
Axe goddess, but you know what I mean.
I simply do what I want, just like I always have.
If you're not having fun, you're not living.
Yeah, true.
So do you have feelings for Lukua?
Where'd that come from?
Who knows.
But for example, what if Lukua was hanging all over your friends or classmates,
and there was nothing you could do but watch them?
What would be going through your mind if that happened?
Hey, I'm sorry.
You don't have to say anything.
I think I get it.
That's what I thought.
He'd be horrifically uncomfortable.
Wait, where are you going?
I stayed for an hour.
I was just about to look for you, Miss Kobayashi.
Oh, you look good in that one.
Aw, thank you so much!
Is everyone over there?
Hey.
Do you want to take a walk?
Just you and me?
I would love to!
What's gotten into you, Miss Kobayashi?
Have you finally come to appreciate my unique and powerful charms?
What?
You're one of the strongest dragons, even capable of fighting the gods.
But here you're able to make friends with anyone whenever you feel like it.
Lately, I've been wondering, after hearing everything you've been through in the past,
how am I worthy of being loved by such an incredible person?
You've really been thinking about that?
I suppose I did share a few too many heavy stories.
Here you are living with me like you never used to fear and hate humans.
You must be constantly reminded of the many things you had to go through.
Oh yeah, and you're also a dragon, so there's that.
That's what keeps repeating in my head.
So what?
Anyway, I guess it's fine.
Even though it's a pain in the A sometimes.
Anyway, that's been my dilemma.
But what about you, Toru?
What's on your mind?
Want to know about my feelings?
Well, you know I love you, Miss Kobayashi.
I feel this way even though you're just a human.
And even though we are better than you.
Better than all humans, really.
I'm sure you're not surprised.
I am a dragon, and I take pride in that.
I've been places where you have to risk your life
and put everything on the line to prove your superiority.
But my heart...
When it came to love, I had no idea how to prove my feelings.
I wondered, would it be easier if I were a better fighter?
Or smarter?
I wished I could be those things.
I spent so much time trying to convince everyone I was.
I guess I was trying to be an adult.
But I realized I didn't have to try to be anything.
It was okay to just be myself.
And you're the one who helped me realize that, Miss Kobayashi.
You're giving me too much credit again.
I think it's a good sign that you're so unaware of it yourself.
Because it means you were meant to save me whether you wanted to or not.
Miss Kobayashi, I love you so much!
From this moment on, forever and ever...
Toro?
Yes?
You're weird.
So did you take any cool photos at the summer festival?
I did.
Wanna see?
Nice.
Looks like you had a great time.
We did.
Hey, you wanna look at flowers?
It is way too hot to be outside all day, ma'am.
What if I said I knew someone whose flesh turns into flowers?
They gave me some, but it wouldn't be right to enjoy them by myself.
Huh.
Blush into flowers?
Why not?
It seems like the kind of thing you'd enjoy immensely.
And I'll make sure it's the perfect day.
I don't get why you're so into this.
Ugh.
Come on.
Everyone has something that could be healed with flowers.
Oh.
But for now, let me get you some more yummy soup.
Hmm.
Oh.
This is someone's flesh?
It looks just like cherry blossoms.
Gorgeous, isn't it?
Well, I packed us a little liquid lunch, so let me know when you're all ready.
Oh, I'm ready.
Ahem.
If it's okay with you, I'll introduce myself as the emcee.
First things first, thank you all for joining us today for Miss Kobayashi's official flower viewing.
We have several things to do, and they were all crafted with Miss Kobayashi in mind.
So, Linda, hand where you can and make sure that she's having the best...
I don't know what you're trying to pull, but cut it out!
Huh?
This mochi's so good!
Now that's what I'm talking about.
There's something so satisfying about drinking booze and enjoying nature.
Huh?
Enjoying nature, huh?
You say that as though humans are so far removed from nature.
Yeah, you're right.
Maybe that's just what happens when we try to seek beauty objectively and share it with each other.
Uh...
You guys should've just stayed home. What's the point?
Nah, this is the best part of this shit, nicks.
Takia, I need you to stay focused.
It's gonna take all of us to sever the tail.
Are you in or are you fired?
It's amazing how much you rely on each other.
Ugh.
Shota, you're getting in on this too?
I guess it's mostly girls out here. I feel so awkward.
Makes sense.
What's going on?
Are you bored?
Elma?
Right.
Time for me to strip down and show you what I've got.
Huh?
Wow!
Okay, what's this nonsense about?
I heard it was common to perform a thing or two at events like these.
I did some research and found that this was the best.
You really went all half for it.
Usually it's just old men that do that, not young, beautiful women.
Whoa!
I guess he likes it.
And there's her.
So pathetic!
She has her own reasons.
Oh.
Next time I'll do that for Saikawa.
Oh, so cute. I'll show it to Take.
Please, I wish you wouldn't.
Can you feel it? Everyone's so excited!
It's almost time for the competition, so please draw to determine the brackets.
What are we doing?
Arm wrestling competition!
Did you draw the two arms on that box?
You're really good, Lady Toru.
Yep.
You don't expect me to join in, do you?
No, I just want you to be our judge.
Okay, that's better.
Come on.
It's your turn to draw, Mr. Fafnir.
Coming through!
And we're ready for the first round.
Takia versus Ululu.
Are you sure you want to do this?
Yeah. What else am I doing?
Okay.
Whatever.
Ready, get set, and...
Go!
I think I broke some bones.
Oh, kind of shocked it wasn't something worse than that.
Is he okay?
Takia is always surprising me with his mad resilience.
Next up, Kana and Lukua.
I want to see a fair match.
Ready?
Go!
You can't use both hands.
It's not as easy as it looks, is it?
You ready, kid?
No, not at all!
Shota, baby! You can do it!
It would mean the world to me if I defeated you.
I expected this from Toru, but Lukua?
I thought at least Fafnir would participate.
Don't talk about me.
Maybe you just got rusty from holding up all the time?
Oh, bite me.
That reminds me.
I think this is the first time you and I have ever fought one-on-one, even though it's only
a game.
I have no doubt in my mind that's how you see it.
We'll play for real now.
Ah!
Oh!
Oh, oh!
Oh, oh, oh, oh!
Oh, oh.
Oh, oh, oh!
I have no doubt in my mind that's how you see it.
We'll play for real, huh?
She's so strong!
I'm going to lose!
You can do it, Toru!
Huh? He's not cheering for me?
Here we go!
Winner, Toru!
Heck yeah!
Lady Toru!
I'm impressed.
Shoot him, baby!
Tell me why!
It's called bribery!
It works, too.
Here is your magic crystal.
You're kidding!
And Toru the Best Mate is the grand prize winner!
Yay!
Whoa!
Whoa?
Wow, you really do drink a lot, don't you, Miss Kobayashi?
Wow, you really do drink a lot, don't you, Ms. Kobayashi?
Wanna share with me?
Oh, of course.
Load me up, Captain.
I feel that.
It's so delicious, too.
This is just the best feeling ever.
I agree.
Look how beautiful the sunset is right now.
Ugh, gorgeous.
It's a belly dance.
You're back to work again tomorrow, right?
Yeah.
It's gonna come and catch you.
But let's not talk about work.
We've got a few more blissful hours.
Right?
Okay, the liquor's a-flowin'.
The party is in full swing!
That doesn't sound good.
What's up?
The cherry blossoms are fluttering, and we have the perfect witnesses for what happens next.
It's time for the main event!
What you've all been waiting for.
Today, me and Ms. Kobayashi will pledge our undying love to one another.
Wedding time!
Wedding!
What's wrong with her?
And now, it's time for a wardrobe change!
What the- get it off!
It's fine, Ms. Kobayashi.
All you have to do is tell me you love me back!
I...
You...
Yes!
You idiot!
I-
This week on Who's Rotten?
Libra!